shopcade.com 2018-11-25

# Shopcade

Shopvolution Limited ("we", "us" or "our") is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy (together with our [Terms of Service](http://www.shopcade/tc) ) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

For data protection purposes, the data controller is Shopvolution Limited, incorporated and registered in the England and Wales (number 07431086), whose registered office is at 131-151 Great Titchfield Street, W1W 5BB London, United Kingdom.

## Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

* Information that you provide to us when creating a Shopcade account via our Site [www.shopcade.com](https://www.shopcade.com/) or on our mobile applications (our "Service") including, but not limited to, name, location and email address.

* Information that you allow us to collect from Social Network Services by linking your account on any Social Network Service, such as Facebook, Google, Twitter, or Instagram, to your Shopcade account. As an example, when connecting your Facebook account, this includes your Facebook user account information including, but not limited to, information such as age, name, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID, list of friends and such friends' user IDs and any other information you have made available through your settings on Facebook.

* Details of your activities on our Site or Service including, but not limited to, any purchases you make through our Site or Service or participation in any games or contests.

* Details of your use of our Site or Service including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data.

* Any data you upload to our Site or Service including posts, reviews and comments or any personal data we fetch from any other websites or services which you authorize us to do.

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Site or Service.

We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

## IP Addresses and cookies

When you use our Service, whether as a registered user or not, we may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. If you have linked your Facebook account with your Shopcade account, we may also collect such information from your Facebook friends and other Facebook users who use the Service. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. When you create a Shopcade account and when you use the Service, we place a cookie file on the hard drive of your computer so that we can collect the information we need to deliver the Service. By using our Service, you agree to our use of cookies for this purpose.

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve the Service and to deliver a better and more personalized service.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies or by clearing your cookies. Please refer to your computer or browser manual on how to do this. However, cookies are essential for our Service to operate. If you disable your cookies, your use of our Service will be adversely affected. 

Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.

## Where we store your personal data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored in, countries outside the UK and the EEA for the purpose of operating our Service and some data processing may be carried out by third parties on our behalf (such as a third party host). By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

You are responsible for keeping confidential any password which enables you to access certain parts of the Service, whether a password has been given to you by us, chosen by you or generated using a third party platform such as Facebook. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we use all reasonable efforts to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site or Service; any transmission is at your own risk.

## Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways: 

* To provide our Site or Service to you and ensure that content on the Service is presented in the most effective and relevant manner for you.

* To provide you with information, products or services including, but not limited to, from our partner merchants that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, unless you have opted out of receiving such information, products or services.

* To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

* To allow you to participate in interactive features of the Service, when you choose to do so.

* To notify you about changes to the Service.

## Disclosure of your information

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, affiliates or partner merchants, but we may provide them with aggregate statistical information and analytics about our users and non-registered visitors habits and use of our Sites and Service.

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

* In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

* If Shopvolution or substantially all of its assets is acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its users will be one of the transferred assets.

* If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements including Facebook’s terms of use; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Shopvolution, our users, or partner merchants and others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Third parties

The Service may, from time to time, contain links to and from third party websites of our partner networks, advertisers, partner merchants, retailers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

## Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcome and should be addressed to [feedback@shopcade.com](mailto:feedback@shopcade.com) or Shopvolution Limited, Privacy Office, 131-151 Great Titchfield Street, W1W 5BB London, United Kingdom

* * *

**1\. Why do you have a Cookies Policy?**    ****

1.1 The reason we have a Cookies Policy is to explain to you what cookies and similar technologies we use, why we use them, and what you need to do if you want to restrict, block, disable or delete them. Our Cookies Policy is part of, and is subject to, our Privacy policy <https://www.shopcade.com/privacy/en> and our Terms of Service <https://www.shopcade.com/tc/en>  

1.2 By accessing and/or using our website you confirm that you accept the terms of this Cookies Policy. 

**2\. About Cookies**

2.1 A cookie is a text file placed on your computer, tablet, mobile phone, or other device (" **device** ") when a person access or uses a website. There are also technologies similar to cookies (e.g. clear gifs) that do the same. Data is collected because it can be necessary to a website’s operation, to assess and/or improve its performance, and/or to provide a personalised experience etc. 

2.2 Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.

2.3 Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

2.4 To find out more general information about cookies, please visit  <https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/online/cookies/>. 

**3.** **Cookies that we use**  

3.1 We use the following cookies for the following purposes:

**Cookie**

| 

**Name**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---|---  
  
Session cookie

| 

PHPSESSID

| 

To identify you when you visit our website and as you navigate our website  
  
User tracking cookie

| 

sc_cid

| 

To report on pages viewed and clicked  
  
Website language selected

| 

sc_lang_

| 

To store your preferences for the language of the website  
  
Cobranding cookie

| 

cobranding

| 

To display a cobranded Elle or Public banner when users are coming from Elle.fr or Public.fr  
  
Website country cookie

| 

cc-persist

| 

To store your preferences for the country of the website  
  
optimizelyEndUserId ; cobranding ; fbm_* ; fbsr_* ; G_ENABLED_IDPS ; __lc_visitor_id_8428301 ; cto_sid ; cto_idcpy ; t_fdz_octapid ; __adroll_bounced ; _bfa ; _bfs ; opera-interstitial ; CAMPAIGN_COOKIE ; VISITOR_COOKIE ; mindsparktb_207743773 ; mindsparktb_207743773 ; monitor_count ; __lnkrntafu |   |  Added by 3rd party partners on our domain. Used for performance optimization, and tracking.  
  
3.3 We use the following _third-party cookies_ on our website. They are placed on your device by the third parties set out below. **Please note that these cookies are subject to the privacy and cookie policies of the third party placing the relevant cookies** **.**

**Cookie**

| 

**Name**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---|---  
Facebook cookies | fbm_ ; fbsr_ | Cookies used for Facebook to identify a user that connects or register through Facebook authentication  
Google Analytics cookies | _ga ; _gid ; _dc_gtm_UA-21721565-2 ; _gat_UA-21721565-2 ; _gat ; __utma ; _utmz ; _utmc ; _utmb ; _utmt | [Google Analytics gathers information about our website use and it is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google's privacy policy is available at: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)  
Optimizely cookies | optimizelyBuckets ; optimizelyEndUserId ; optimizelySegments | To create AB Test scenarios on our website in order to improve user experience based on AB tests results.  
Google Adwords | cto_lwid ; _sm_au | These cookies are used by Google to collect anonymous information for use on Google Adwords. The data is anonymous and helps Google deliver relevant advertising on other websites. The cookies expire between thirteen months and two years.  
Google DoubleClick cookies | __ar_v4 | Optimises ad display based on the user's movement combined and various advertiser bids for displaying user ads.  
Hubspot cookies | hubspotutk ; hsfirstvisit ; __hstc | Customer relationship management tool used to improve customer satisfaction  
AB Tasty cookies | ABTasty ; ABTastySession | To create AB Test scenarios on our website in order to improve user experience based on AB tests results.  
Wordpress cookies | tk_lr ; tk_r3d ; tk_or ; SL_GWPT_Show_Hide_tmp ; SL_wptGlobTipTmp; tk_ai ; tk_qs ; SLG_GWPT_Show_Hide_tmp ; SLG_wptGlobTipTmp | Collection of internal metrics for user activity, used to improve user experience. We use these cookies to make the use of the site more convenient. Some common uses of cookies include the ability to save browsing preferences related to the language of use of the site or the ability to share on social networks links and content on the site  
Stripe cookies | __stripe_sid ; __stripe_mid | These cookies are used by Stripe to process payments on the website  
AppDynamics cookie | ADRUM | This cookie is used to detect errors on the website - this information is sent to the website's support staff in order to optimize the visitor's experience on the website.  
CloudFlare cookie | __cfduid | This cookie is used to identify individual clients behind a shared IP address and apply security settings on a per-client basis. This cookie is absolutely necessary for supporting Cloudflare's security features and cannot be turned off.  
Livechat | lc_visitor_id | Used for livechat https://www.livechatinc.com/  
| t_fdz_octapid |   
| _bfa ; _bfs |   
Opera ads cookie | opera-interstitial | Set for some users on the Opera browser. We do not set this cookie  
| CAMPAIGN_COOKIE ; VISITOR_COOKIE |   
wildfig media session cookie | __lnkrntdmcvrd | https://www.wildfigmedia.com/ seo company.  
Mindspark | mindsparktb_207743773 ; mindsparktb_222250168 ; mindsparktb_226333724 ; mindsparktb_227257322 ;   
mindsparktbsupport_227257322 ; mindspark_extension_api_features_227257322 ; mindsparktb_232530392 ; mindsparktbsupport_232530392 ; mindspark_extension_api_features_232530392 | We do not set this cookie - these are set by the mindspark browser extension, which some users might have installed  
| monitor_count |   
| _ju_dn |   
| __lnkrntafu |   
| ivbss ; ivbsdid ; ivBlk |   
| mprtcl-v4 | [http://cmcmarkets.com/ ](http://cmcmarkets.com/)  
Demandware cookie | __cq_uuid; __cq_seg |   
Browser cookie | arp_scroll_position | This is a browser based cookie that is used to remember user's position on a page  
CrazyEgg cookie | _ceir | Tool used to identify where users click on a page  
Kissmetrics cookies | km_uq ; km_ai ; km_lv | Marketing tool to help increase conversions, engagement and retention  
AdRoll cookie | __adroll_bounced ; __adroll_bounce_closed | This cookie is used for retargeting when a user comes to visit our products, he might see them on other websites  
  
**4\. What if I don’t want cookies and similar technologies?**

4.1 You can restrict, block, disable or delete cookies and similar technologies.  Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more information please visit <http://cookies.insites.com/disable-cookies/> or <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/>.    

**5\. What happens if you update your Cookies Policy?**

5.1 We may update our Cookies Policy from time to time and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our processing of your data, privacy practices and changes in applicable data protection law and regulations. If we make changes to this Cookies Policy, we will post the revised Cookies Policy on our platform. 

**6\. What do I do if I have any questions?**  
6.1 To contact us with any questions regarding our Cookies Policy, please contact us at [privacy@shopvolution.com](mailto:privacy@shopvolution.com).
